silverprice.org 2016-12-26

# Privacy

SILVERPRICE.ORG Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to silverprice.org is important to us. At silverprice.org, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit silverprice.org, and how we safeguard your information.

We never sell, rent or share in any way your personal information with any third parties. silverprice.org may share non personal aggregate information with third parties such as the number of visitors per day received by silverprice.org or the number of visitors received from a specific country.

Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as Telstra or Optus), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. These log files are stored by google analytics.

Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This includes the ability the ability to use some of our features such as our gold price calculator. If your browser is configured to accept Cookies you will see a button at the bottom of the Holdings Calculator. Pressing the button will place a cookie on your machine containing the information you entered into the Holdings Calculator. When you return to silverprice.org the cookie will be retrieved from your machine and the values placed into the calculator. We do not store these values at silverprice.org nor do we ever have access to them.

We also use third party advertisements from google adsense on silverprice.org to support our site. Google adsense uses technology such as cookies and web beacons when they place advertisements on our website, which will send Google information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing usa gold dealer ads to someone in the USA, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing car dealer ads to someone who frequents car sites). You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Email Addresses

We do collect email addresses via google feedburner when you subscribe to receive updates of commentary from gsilverprice.org. These emails are stored on the google.com servers. We do not and will not sell or rent these emails to any other parties. You must double opt in in order to be subscribed to our email lists and there is an opt out link at the bottom of every email allowing you to click on them at any time to opt out and stop receiving email from silverprice.org. Should you have any problems in doing this please do not hesitate to contact us and we will manually unsubscribe your email and allow you to opt out of the emails.

Forum

The goldprice.org forum was closed in 2007 and may or may not resume operation in the future. We store your name and email address and password on the goldprice.org servers. If you would like to have your account deleted please contact us and we will be happy to delete your account.

Contacting silverprice.org

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy or how to unsubscribe from our email lists please don't hesitate to contact us:

Email: [goldprice+help@gmail.com](mailto:goldprice+help@gmail.com)

Address:

Gold Price Group Limited.  
9th Floor, Amtel Building  
148 Des Voeux Road Central  
Central, Hong Kong
